<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<list>
	<pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
		<id>no-js-help</id>
		<title>No JavaScript support</title>
		<subtitle></subtitle>
		<body><![CDATA[
		  In order to be able to experience the full functionality of our digital library, you have to turn on JavaScript support in your WWW browser. 
		  Any WWW browser should have options or preferences window in which you can do this.
		  <p>Below there are some examples on how to turn on or off the JavaScript support option for specific WWW browsers::</p>
		  <ul>
			<li>
				<b>FireFox 3.6.x</b> - in top toolbar click Tools -> Options -> Content -> Enable JavaScript
			</li>
			<li>
				<b>Internet Explorer 8</b> - on the right side of top menu click Tools -> Internet options -> Security -> Custom level... -> in the section "Scripting" by selecting
				the option "Active scripting".
			</li>
			<li>
				<b>Opera 10.x</b> in top toolbar click Tools -> Preferences -> Advanced -> Content -> Enable JavaScript  
			</li>
		  </ul>
		  <p>Detailed instructions on turning on and off the JavaScript support can be also found in the WWW browser manual, located in most cases in the “Help” menu.</p>
		 ]]></body>
		<referencesList class="list" />
		<references></references>
    <localeName>en</localeName>
  </pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
  <pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
		<id>no-js-help</id>
		<title>Brak wsparcia dla JavaScript</title>
		<subtitle></subtitle>
		<body><![CDATA[
		  Aby móc w pełni korzystać z możliwości naszej biblioteki cyfrowej, musisz włączyć w swojej przeglądarce WWW obsługę JavaScript.
		  Każda przeglądarka powinna posiadać okno opcji lub preferencji, w którym można to zrobić.
		  <p>Poniżej znajdują się przykłady włączania i wyłączania JavaScript dla konkretnych przeglądarek:</p>
		  <ul>
			<li>
				<b>FireFox w wersji 3.6.x</b> - w górnym menu należy kliknąć w Narzędzia -> Opcje -> Treść -> Włącz obsługę języka JavaScript.  
			</li>
			<li>
				<b>Internet Explorer 8</b> - w górnym menu po prawej stronie należy kliknąć w Narzędzia -> Opcje internetowe -> Zabezpieczenia -> Poziom niestandardowy..., a następnie w sekcji "Obsługa skryptów" włączyć
				opcję "Wykonywanie aktywnych skryptów".
			</li>
			<li>
				<b>Opera 10.x</b> w górnym menu należy kliknąć Narzędzia -> Preferencje -> Zaawansowane -> Zawartość -> Włącz obsługę JavaScript  
			</li>
		  </ul>
		  <p>Szczegółowe instrukcje włączania obsługi JavaScript można znaleźć również w dokumentacji przeglądarki WWW, dostępnej zazwyczaj w menu "Pomoc".</p>
		 ]]></body>
		<referencesList class="list" />
		<references></references>
    <localeName>pl</localeName>
  </pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
  <pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
		<id>powered-by</id>
		<title>Wykorzystane rozwiązania</title>
		<subtitle></subtitle>
		<body>
		<![CDATA[
			<p>
			Oprogramowanie dLibra korzysta z zestawu ikon <b>Silk Icons</b> autorstwa Pana <b>Marka James`a</b>, które dostępne są
			pod adresem: <a href="http://www.famfamfam.com/">www.famfamfam.com</a> oraz z zestawu ikon udostępnionych przez
			firmę <b>FatCow Web Hosting</b>, które można pobrać pod adresem: <a href="http://www.fatcow.com/free-icons/">www.fatcow.com/free-icons</a>.
			<br/>Zarówno Panu James`owi jak i firmie FatCow Web Hosting serdecznie dziękujemy.
			</p>
		 ]]>
		</body>
		<referencesList class="list" />
		<references></references>
		<localeName>pl</localeName>
	</pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
	<pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
		<id>powered-by</id>
		<title>Used solutions</title>
		<subtitle></subtitle>
		<body>
		<![CDATA[
			<p style="color:#999;font-size:11px;">
			The dLibra software extensively uses the Silk Icons set created by Mr Mark James, which is available under
			this address: <a href="http://www.famfamfam.com/">www.famfamfam.com</a> and also icon sets created by FatCow Web Hosting,
			which can be downloaded from this site: <a href="http://www.fatcow.com/free-icons/">www.fatcow.com/free-icons</a>.
			<br/>We thank the producers - Mr James and FatCow Web Hosting company for the opportunity to use those icon sets.
			</p>
		 ]]>
		</body>
		<referencesList class="list" />
		<references></references>
		<localeName>en</localeName>
	</pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
	<pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
		<id>about-dlibra</id>
		<title>O dLibrze...</title>
		<subtitle></subtitle>
		<body>
			<![CDATA[
    <p>
	    <a href="http://dlibra.psnc.pl">dLibra</a> to pierwszy polski system do budowy bibliotek cyfrowych, jest on rozwijany przez 
	    <a href="http://www.man.poznan.pl">Poznańskie Centrum Superkomputerowo - Sieciowe</a> (PCSS)
	    od 1999 roku. Rozpoczęcie prac nad tym systemem było efektem badań w zakresie bibliotek 
	    cyfrowych prowadzonych w PCSS już od 1996 roku. System dLibra jest obecnie 
	    najpopularniejszym tego typu oprogramowaniem w Polsce.
	</p>
	<p>    
		dLibra jest szeroko wykorzystywana przez instytucje takie jak biblioteki akademickie
		i publiczne do udostępniania cyfrowych postaci gromadzonych przez nie zbiorów. 
		Instytucje te, wykorzystując sieć <a href="http://www.pionier.gov.pl">PIONIER</a> i 
		oprogramowanie dLibra, współtworzą polską platformę rozproszonych bibliotek cyfrowych.
		Zachęcamy do zapoznania się z aktualną lista wdrożeń systemu dLibra. PCSS oferuje 
		również szkolenia oraz pomoc techniczną z zakresu wykorzystania oprogramowania dLibra.
	</p>
	<p style="text-align:center">
		<a href="http://dlibra.psnc.pl" target="_blank" title="dlibra">
			<img src="../style/common/img/about/dlibra-logo.jpg" alt="dLibra" />
		</a>
	&nbsp;
		<a href="http://www.man.poznan.pl" target="_blank" title="pcss">
			<img src="../style/common/img/about/psnc.gif" alt="pcss" />
		</a>
	&nbsp;	
		<a href="http://www.pionier.gov.pl/" target="_blank" title="pionier">
			<img src="../style/common/img/about/pionier.gif" alt="pionier" />
		</a>
	</p>
	<br/>
	<hr/>
	<p style="text-align:center"><a href="help?id=powered-by">Wykorzystane rozwiązania</a></p>
	]]>
		</body>
		<referencesList class="list" />
		<references></references>
		<localeName>pl</localeName>
	</pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
	<pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
		<id>about-dlibra</id>
		<title>About dLibra</title>
		<subtitle></subtitle>
		<body>
			<![CDATA[
       <p>
	       <a href="http://dlibra.psnc.pl">dLibra</a> is the first Polish system for building digital libraries, which 
	       has been developed by the <a href="http://www.man.poznan.pl"Poznan Supercomputing and Networking Center</a> (PSNC) since 1999. 
	       dLibra is an effect of research in the field of digital libraries which has been performed in PSNC since 1996.dLibra 
	       system is now the most popular software of this type in Poland. 
       </p>

	   <p>       
	       dLibra enables building professional repositories of digital documents which can be accessed by external 
	       individuals and systems on the Internet. Communication and data exchange is based on well known 
	       standards and protocols such as: RSS, RDF, MARC, DublinCore or OAI-PMH. Digital libraries based on
	       dLibra offer to their users expanded possibilities such as: searching the content of stored elements, 
	       searching bibliographic description with use of synonyms dictionary, grouping digital publications and
	       navigating in these structure or precise and expanded access rules to elements. Detailed functional 
	       description of dLibra can be found <a href="http://dlibra.psnc.pl/html/index.php?option=content&task=view&id=13">here</a>.
	       Description of architecture and technical requirements can be found <a href="http://dlibra.psnc.pl/html/index.php?option=content&task=view&id=14">here</a>.
       </p>

 	   <p>
		   dLibra is used by institutions such as academic and public libraries to make stored digital 
		   publications available on the Internet. These institutions by using <a href="http://www.pionier.gov.pl">PIONIER</a> 
		   network and dLibra software create Polish platform of distributed digital libraries. Current list of installations 
		   of dLibra system is available here. In addition PSNC offers training and technical help in the 
		   field of dLibra system usage.
	   </p>
	   <p>
	     Main dLibra library page based on <a href="http://www.oswd.org/design/preview/id/2876"> 
		 Internet Services by LanVacation</a> template.	      
	  	 Admin panel HTML template based on template by <a href="http://www.minimalistic-design.net">Minimalistic Design</a>.
	   </p>
	   	<p style="text-align:center">
			<a href="http://dlibra.psnc.pl" target="_blank" title="dlibra">
				<img src="../style/common/img/about/dlibra-logo.jpg" alt="dLibra" />
			</a>
		&nbsp;
			<a href="http://www.man.poznan.pl" target="_blank" title="pcss">
				<img src="../style/common/img/about/psnc.gif" alt="pcss" />
			</a>
		&nbsp;	
			<a href="http://www.pionier.gov.pl/" target="_blank" title="pionier">
				<img src="../style/common/img/about/pionier.gif" alt="pionier" />
			</a>
		</p>
		<br/>
		<hr/>
		<p style="text-align:center"><a href="help?id=powered-by">Used solutions</a></p>
		
	   ]]>
		</body>
		<referencesList class="list" />
		<references></references>
		<localeName>en</localeName>
	</pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
	<pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
  		<id>regulations</id>
  		<title>Example page with regulations</title>
  		<subtitle></subtitle>
  		<body><![CDATA[
  		<p>
  			Here should be the regulations acceptable by the user who intends to upload the publication.
  		</p>
  	
	  	<p>
  			Be sure to edit this page before upload will be available to users.
  		</p>
  
  		]]></body>
  		<referencesList class="list" />
  		<references></references>
  		<localeName>en</localeName>
	</pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
	<pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
  		<id>regulations</id>
  		<title>Przykładowa strona z regulaminem</title>
  		<subtitle></subtitle>
  		<body><![CDATA[
  			<p>
  				Tutaj powinien znajdować się regulamin do zaakceptowania przez użytkownika zamierzającego wgrać publikację.
  			</p>
  	
  			<p>
  				Pamiętaj aby zredagować tę stronę zanim udostępnisz czytelnikom możliwość wgrywania publikacji!
  			</p>
  		]]></body>
  		<referencesList class="list" />
  		<references></references>
  		<localeName>pl</localeName>
	</pl.psnc.dlibra.web.comp.resources.item.HelpItem>
</list>